{
    "0": {
        "document": "Norway: Fiscal compensation for the scrapping of fossil vans when converting to a zero-emission van.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9164777398109436,
            "1": 0.083522267639637
        }
    },
    "1": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Northern Powerhouse Investment Fund (NPIF) will invest a further £390 million by 2020-21 to support ultra-low emission vehicles (ULEVs), renewable fuels, and connected and autonomous vehicles (CAVs). This includes £80 million for ULEV charging infrastructure, £150 million in support for low emission buses and taxis, £20 million for the development of alternative aviation and heavy goods vehicle fuels, and £100 million for new UK CAV testing infrastructure. In addition to the tax incentives for ULEVs in company tax and salary schemes set out in the tax chapter, from today to the end of March 2019 the government will also offer 100% first-year allowances to companies investing in charge-points for electric vehicles. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Northern Powerhouse Investment Fund",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NPIF",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "£390 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "2020-21",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "£80 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "ULEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "£150 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "£20 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "£100 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "today",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the end of March 2019",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "100%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "first-year",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.6136073470115662,
            "1": 0.38639265298843384
        }
    },
    "2": {
        "document": "Norway: The Norwegian Government Environmental Fund is a loan scheme administered by the Norwegian Industrial and Regional Development Fund. The scheme was established to provide funding for projects that help to reduce emissions of greenhouse gases and other environmentally harmful gases, and provide funding for energy efficiency investments. \"Oko-bygg\" is a development programme that was started in 1998. It provides information, advice and grants to promote the use of eco-efficient technology, including more efficient and flexible energy use in the construction industry. The programme will end in 2002. The Norwegian State Housing Bank offers various loan and grant schemes for residential energy efficiency measures. From 2002 the housing bank also offers NKr 140 000 in extra loans and NKr 10 000 in grants to homebuilders who invest in water heating systems based on bioenergy, solar or that use heat pumps. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Norwegian Government Environmental Fund",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Norwegian Industrial and Regional Development Fund",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "1998",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2002",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "The Norwegian State Housing Bank",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2002",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the housing bank",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "140",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "10 000",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9952572584152222
        }
    },
    "3": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Home Energy Scotland Advice Network consists of of local advice centres covering all of Scotland. Expert advisors offer free advice on energy saving, keeping warm at home, renewable energy, greener travel, cutting water waste and more. Funded by the Scottish Government and managed by the Energy Saving Trust, its mission is to help people in Scotland create warmer homes, reduce their bills and help tackle climate change. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Home Energy Scotland Advice Network",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Scotland",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Scottish Government",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Energy Saving Trust",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Scotland",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.5013142824172974,
            "1": 0.49868568778038025
        }
    },
    "4": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Legislative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom:",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.2080838829278946,
            "1": 0.7919161319732666
        }
    },
    "5": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The United Kingdom's LTS refers to its 2050 net zero target enshrined in law since 2019. The strategy is structured around 4 key principles:\n1. To work with the grain of consumer choice: no one will be required to rip out their existing boiler or scrap their current car\n2. To ensure the biggest polluters pay the most for the transition through fair carbon pricing\n3. To ensure that the most vulnerable are protected through Government supportin the form of energy bill discounts, energy efficiency upgrades, and more\n4. To work with businesses to continue delivering deep cost reductions in low carbon tech through support for the latest state of the art kit to bring down costs for consumers and deliver benefits for businesses.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The United Kingdom's",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2019",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "4",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "1",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "3",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "4",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9930269718170166
        }
    },
    "6": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Ministry for Housing, Communities and Local Government (DCLG) is responsible for making sure buildings in the UK meet the standards required by the EU Energy Performance of Buildings Directive. The Directive requires that all properties (homes, commercial and public buildings) must have an Energy Performance Certificate (EPC) when sold, built or rented; larger public buildings over 500m must display a Display Energy Certificate (DEC); all air-conditioning systems over 12 kW must be regularly inspected by an Energy Assessor. EPCs are produced by accredited energy assessors using standard methods and assumptions about energy usage. This means that the energy efficiency of one building can easily be compared with another building of the same type. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Ministry for Housing, Communities and Local Government",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the EU Energy Performance of Buildings Directive",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Directive",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "an Energy Performance Certificate",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "500",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Display Energy Certificate",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "DEC",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "12",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "one",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9908066987991333
        }
    },
    "7": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The 2023 Green Finance Strategy reinforces the UK government's stance on green finance and investment. It delineates five key objectives, including mobilizing financial support for climate-oriented projects, encouraging private investment in the green economy, and aligning global financial flows with climate and nature objectives.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2023",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "five",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9816672205924988,
            "1": 0.018332796171307564
        }
    },
    "8": {
        "document": "Norway: Investment aid to implement energy efficiency measures in existing commercial and public buildings, including building cooperations. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9742962121963501,
            "1": 0.025703808292746544
        }
    },
    "9": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This strategy is a follow-up to the UK's Hydrogen Strategy, and it increases the 2030 capacity target from 5GW to 10GW.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Hydrogen Strategy",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "5GW",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "10GW",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.5514527559280396,
            "1": 0.44854721426963806
        }
    },
    "10": {
        "document": "Norway: Legislative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.2516045868396759,
            "1": 0.7483953833580017
        }
    },
    "11": {
        "document": "Norway: With the ratification of the Kigali Amendment, group I parties commit to peak HFCs consumption by 2019 and reduce it to 15% of 2012 levels by 2036",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Kigali Amendment",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2019",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "15%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2012",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2036",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.02612924575805664,
            "1": 0.9738707542419434
        }
    },
    "12": {
        "document": "Norway: This strategy focuses particularly on certain priorities for promoting green competitiveness:\n• markets for green solutions;\n• green and innovative public procurement;\n• research, innovation and technology development;\n• infrastructure for green solutions;\n• managing climate-related risks and financing:\n• a circular economy;\n• increasing exports of green solutions;\n• continued dialogue and cooperation with the business sector",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.03600732982158661,
            "1": 0.9639926552772522
        }
    },
    "13": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Budget (2021) brings a policy framework outlining carbon pricing, energy taxes and transport taxes as a way forward towards achievement of net zero targets.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2021",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.971691370010376,
            "1": 0.028308648616075516
        }
    },
    "14": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: A sum of money is collected from all electricity customers through a Public Service Obligation (PSO) which is used to provide funding for energy efficiency and renewable energy schemes. Previously known as the Energy Efficiency Levy (EEL), it is now known as the Northern Ireland Sustainable Energy Programme (NISEP). The strategic objectives of the NISEP are to contribute to the achievement of: Efficiency in the use of energy; Socially and environmentally sustainable long-term energy supplies at best value to customers whilst also having due regard to vulnerable customers. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "a Public Service Obligation",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Energy Efficiency Levy",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "EEL",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Northern Ireland Sustainable Energy Programme",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NISEP",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NISEP",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Socially",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9926449060440063
        }
    },
    "15": {
        "document": "Norway: From 1999 to 2017, municipal parkings were free for EV owners. Since 2017, municipal authorities can decide if they continue offering free parking for such vehicles.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "1999",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2017",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "EV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2017",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.03472054377198219,
            "1": 0.9652794599533081
        }
    },
    "16": {
        "document": "Norway: This strategy seeks to prioritise efforts in the areas in which Norway has a particular advantage, where Norway and Norwegian companies and technology communities can influence development, and where there are opportunities for increased value creation and green growth. Its main objectives are:\n- continue to support the necessary technological developments. The authorities will monitor developments and adjust the policy instruments if needed.\n- evaluate policy instruments to promote the development and use of hydrogen in Norway.\n- support research into, and the development and demonstration of hydrogen technologies through relevant schemes, with a focus on projects of a high scientific quality and potential for commercial development.\n- contribute to developing technology for the capture, transport and storage of CO2, and has ambitions to build cost-effective solutions for full-scale CCS plants in Norway, given that this will generate technology development in an international per\u0002spective",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Norwegian",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "CCS",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9942951798439026
        }
    },
    "17": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This policy seeks to align vehicle emissions standards from the UK with those of the EU. It stipulates a limit of 95g CO2/km for new passenger vehicles and 147g CO2/km for vans from 2020, as well as a 15% emissions reduction below a 2021 baseline for both cars and vans, and from 2030, this will increase to a 37.5% reduction below the 2021 baseline.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "EU",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "95",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "147",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2020",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "15%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2021",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "37.5%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2021",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.015952354297041893,
            "1": 0.9840476512908936
        }
    },
    "18": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The UK's Market Transformation Programme (MTP) effective since 1997 undertakes policy research, development and support projects that aim to bring forward products, systems and services that do less harm to the environment, using less energy, water and other resources over their lifetime. The MTP provides strategic support to a growing set of product policies. These aim to encourage resource efficiency through the development of supply-chain measures such as reliable product information, raising minimum standards and encouraging best practice and where consensus and joined-up thinking is essential to establish priorities and to deliver practical policies. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Market Transformation Programme",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "1997",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9924750328063965
        }
    },
    "19": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The UK Net Zero Research and Innovation Framework entails a government investment exceeding £4 billion from 2022 to 2025. This funding is dedicated to the development of technologies crucial for achieving the nation's net zero goals. It emphasizes supporting businesses within the green economy and addressing urgent challenges that the market may struggle to tackle independently.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The UK Net Zero Research",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Innovation Framework",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "£4 billion",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "2022",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2025",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9865235090255737,
            "1": 0.013476477935910225
        }
    },
    "20": {
        "document": "Norway: Enova offers investment aid to energy measures in buildings. The aid is given to measures that reduce energy use and converts energy sources to renewable ones. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Enova",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9818306565284729,
            "1": 0.018169360235333443
        }
    },
    "21": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: ESOS is a mandatory energy assessment scheme for organisations in the UK that meet the qualification criteria. The Environment Agency is the UK scheme administrator.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom:",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "ESOS",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Environment Agency",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9722244143486023,
            "1": 0.027775589376688004
        }
    },
    "22": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Municipal application of the Go Ultra Low City Scheme (GULCS). London’s bid was awarded £13m in capital funding to drive the uptake of ultra-low emission vehicles in the period 2015/16 - 2019/20. The bid was ambitious, wanting London to become the “Go Ultra-Low emission vehicle Capital”.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom: Municipal",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Go Ultra Low City Scheme",
                "WORK_OF_ART"
            ],
            [
                "13",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "2015/16 - 2019/20",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "London",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Capital”.",
                "ORG"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9806884527206421,
            "1": 0.019311539828777313
        }
    },
    "23": {
        "document": "Norway: Legislative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.2516056001186371,
            "1": 0.7483943700790405
        }
    },
    "24": {
        "document": "Norway: A system of informative electricity bills was introduced in Norway in 2002. All customers expected to consume more than 8,000 kWh per year receive bills from the grid company for actual consumption. Customers previously paid on the basis of estimated consumption. In addition, the bill must show how the customers electricity consumption compares with the year before and specifies where advice on energy saving can be obtained. The aim is to make customers more aware of their electricity consumption. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2002",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "more than 8,000",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "the year before",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9904834032058716
        }
    },
    "25": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: New Minimum Energy Efficiency Standards in England and Wales came into force on 1st April 2018, requiring all rental properties to have a minimum Energy Performance Certificate rating of E. The regulations came into force for new lets and renewals of tenancies in April 2018 and will apply to all existing tenancies from April 2020. It will be unlawful to rent a property below the minimum E rating, unless there is an applicable exemption. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom:",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "England",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Wales",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "1st April 2018",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "April 2018",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "April 2020",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.17710255086421967,
            "1": 0.8228974342346191
        }
    },
    "26": {
        "document": "Norway: Enova offers investment aid to energy efficiency measures, conversion to the use of renewable energy sources and energy recovery in the industry. Capital totalling about NOK 2.6 billion is transferred to the fund each year, including about NOK 630 million per year from an earmarked levy on the grid tariff. These financial arrangements make it possible for Enova to be a predictable and flexible source of funding for projects. From 2017, Enova’s focus has been shifted more towards climate-related activities and innovation, in line with the new agreement for the period 2017–2020. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Enova",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2.6 billion",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "each year",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "630 million",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Enova",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2017",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Enova’s",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2017–2020",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9928967952728271
        }
    },
    "27": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The UK's NDC covers all sectors and gases. For CO2, CH4 and N2O the reference year is 1990 and for F-gases the reference year is 1995. The UK’s overall absolute target is to reduce GHG emissions at least by 68% (including LULUCF) by 2030 compared with reference levels. Emissions from International Aviation and Shipping are not included.\nThe UK has a policy framework in force establishing the binding commitment of net zero emissions by 2050, and Scotland sets bolder goals to reach net-zero in 2045 and 75% below 1990 by 2030. Wales pledges at least 80% reduction by 2050. \nThe Climate Change Act introduced carbon budgets for the UK Government, which cap emissions over successive five-year periods and must be set 12 years in advance.\nThe UK government is putting into force the Clean Growth Strategy, which is a Ten Point Plan for a green industrial revolution, encompassing clean energy, buildings, transport and technologies. Moreover, the government pushes for individual plans across key sectors such as Energy White Paper, Transport Decarbonisation Plan and Heat and Buildings Strategy (UK NDC, 2020).\nUK’s NDC establishes a reduction of 68% of 1990 levels including LULUCF emissions. If LULUCF is excluded, this is equivalent to 69% or 251 MtCO2e. CAT classifies this as strong target and once the UK adopts national policies (2030 ban on the sale of fossil fuel cars and a ramping up of renewable energy investment, particularly into offshore wind) it will bring their emissions in line with the 1.5°C goal. Also, the UK has a net-zero goal by 2050. CAT cannot rate, at this moment, the UK target due to complexities derived from Brexit (Climate Action Tracker, 2021).\n ",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "NDC",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "CO2",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "CH4",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the reference year",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "1990",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "F",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the reference year is 1995",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "GHG",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "68%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "International Aviation",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Scotland",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2045",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "75%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "1990",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "at least 80%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "The Climate Change Act",
                "LAW"
            ],
            [
                "the UK Government",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "five-year",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "12 years",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Clean Growth Strategy",
                "LAW"
            ],
            [
                "Ten",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Energy White Paper, Transport Decarbonisation Plan and Heat and Buildings Strategy",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2020",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "NDC",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "68%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "1990",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "69%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "251",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "CAT",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "1.5",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "CAT",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Brexit",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "2021",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "1": 0.9954286813735962
        }
    },
    "28": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: With the ratification of the Kigali Amendment, group I parties commit to peak HFCs consumption by 2019 and reduce it to 15% of 2012 levels by 2036",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Kigali Amendment",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2019",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "15%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2012",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2036",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.025581754744052887,
            "1": 0.9744182229042053
        }
    },
    "29": {
        "document": "Norway: Enova offers investment aid to full-scale demonstration projects involving new energy and climate technology under real-life operating conditions. Enova has a distinct responsibility for an initiative directed towards new energy and climate technologies in industry. The efforts shall contribute to a reduction in greenhouse gas emissions and support the development of energy diversification in the long run, through the development and market introduction of new technologies and new solutions that can contribute to this. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Enova",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Enova",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9904007911682129
        }
    },
    "30": {
        "document": "Norway: In November 2002, the Government issued a White Paper on the domestic use of natural gas. The White Paper puts forward a strategy in order to increase the use of natural gas in Norway. The policy is focused on direct use of natural gas and power plants with carbon dioxide capture and storage. In addition, the report evaluates measures to boost transmission of land-generated electricity to offshore installation, hydrogen and a system of green certificates. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "November 2002",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Government",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.991470992565155
        }
    },
    "31": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Offshore Wind Net Zero Investment Roadmap sets targets aiming to deploy up to 50GW of offshore wind energy by 2030, with an additional capacity of up to 5GW in floating offshore wind. This initiative is integral to the UK's energy security enhancement, facilitating the decarbonization of its power system by 2035, and ultimately achieving its net zero emissions target by 2050.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "5GW",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2035",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.5426138639450073,
            "1": 0.4573861360549927
        }
    },
    "32": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The UK government has announced a plan to achieve its net zero targets, including a Carbon Budget Delivery Update with proposals and policies to meet carbon budgets. Additionally, there's a focus on advancing the new nuclear programme, establishing a taskforce for solar power ambitions, and making long-term commitments to Carbon Capture, Utilization, and Storage (CCUS).",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Carbon Capture, Utilization",
                "ORG"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9839541912078857,
            "1": 0.016045818105340004
        }
    },
    "33": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Transport for London’s July 2015 ULEV Delivery Plan committed to deliver 300 rapid charge points by 2020, with 150 by 2018, to meet the expected demand from taxis and commercial fleets. The government is supporting this ambition with a total of £12.6m of funding. Many chargepoints will be introduced by Local Authorities and the private market in England or London in the coming years. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom: Transport for London’s",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "July 2015",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "300",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2020",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "150",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2018",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "12.6",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "Local Authorities",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "England",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "London",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the coming years",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9872671961784363,
            "1": 0.012732770293951035
        }
    },
    "34": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Legislative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom:",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.20807145535945892,
            "1": 0.7919285893440247
        }
    },
    "35": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Vans were to go electric and lorries to run on hydrogen dual-fuel under a £20 million government programme to cut emissions and improve air quality. The funding, announced at the Sustainable Road Transport Conference, in central London, was being given to 20 firms who set out plans for innovative ways to deploy low and zero emission vehicles. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom: Vans",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "£20 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "the Sustainable Road Transport Conference",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "London",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "20",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9841773509979248,
            "1": 0.015822634100914
        }
    },
    "36": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The government will make available a budget of two billion pounds to build protected cycle lanes, provide cycle training for everyone and and increase access to e-bikes. The plan encompasses also a consult to strengthen the Highway Code for safety purposes and create low traffic neighbourhoods to improve air quality. \nIn sum, the strategy's target is to foster walking and cycling by improve street conditions, increase security of people while cycling and through informational programmes to the decision of cycling/walking be firstly considered by citizens.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "two billion pounds",
                "QUANTITY"
            ],
            [
                "the Highway Code",
                "LAW"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9905286431312561
        }
    },
    "37": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The government will spend more than £600 million between 2015-16 and 2020-21 to support uptake and manufacturing of ultra-low emission vehicles (ULEVs) in the UK, maintaining the global leadership that has seen 1 in 4 of all European electric vehicles built here and keep the UK on track for all new cars to be effectively zero emission by 2040. This investment will save 65 million tonnes of carbon and help deliver the Long-Term answer on urban air quality. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "more than £600 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "between 2015-16",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "1",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "4",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "European",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2040",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "65 million tonnes",
                "QUANTITY"
            ],
            [
                "the Long-Term",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9855504631996155,
            "1": 0.014449523761868477
        }
    },
    "38": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Go Ultra Low City Scheme is a programme by the Office for Low Emission Vehicles within the Department for Transport. It aims to provide funding to local authorities in the UK that encourages thousands of people to consider switching to an electric car.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Office for Low Emission Vehicles",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Department for Transport",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "thousands",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9835596084594727,
            "1": 0.016440343111753464
        }
    },
    "39": {
        "document": "Norway: The EFTA Surveillance Authority (ESA) has today approved an extension of the VAT exemption for electric cars until the end of 2022.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The EFTA Surveillance Authority",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "ESA",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "today",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "VAT",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the end of 2022",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.615667998790741,
            "1": 0.38433200120925903
        }
    },
    "40": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Incentives for EVs such as free parking are decided at local level. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom:",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.43199265003204346,
            "1": 0.5680072903633118
        }
    },
    "41": {
        "document": "Norway: \"In January 2008, the Norwegian government revised its previous target, announced in 2007, of becoming carbon netural by 2050 to 2030. This earlier target was reached through agreement between the Norwegian government and the opposition parties. The idea of the target is to reduce net emissions of carbon dioxide to zero by 2030 through both emissions reducing projects in Norway and elsewhere. Activities will include investing in projects to slow deforestation in developing countries, investing in renewable energy and carbon capture and storage research, raising a tax on diesel fuel, investing in mass transport and a wide range of other measures.\" (IEA, PAMS) IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "January 2008",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Norwegian",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "2007",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2050 to 2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Norwegian",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "IEA",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9917290210723877
        }
    },
    "42": {
        "document": "Norway: This document presents the government's strategy to meet its climate commitments for 2030. It discusses sectoral performances and examines ways to further reduce emissions.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9667001366615295,
            "1": 0.03329985961318016
        }
    },
    "43": {
        "document": "Norway: This support scheme for wind power production corresponding to half of the consumer electricity tax was introduced in 1999.\nIn 2001 the consumer tax on electricity was NOK 0.113/kWh, giving an incentive of NOK 0.0565/kWh of wind power produced. In 2002 the consumer tax on electricity was NOK 0.093/kWh, giving an incentive of NOK 0.0465/kWh of wind power produced. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "half",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "1999",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2001",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NOK 0.0565",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2002",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NOK 0.0465",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9895409941673279,
            "1": 0.0104589918628335
        }
    },
    "44": {
        "document": "Norway: The National Transport Plan 2022–2033 (Report No 20 to the Storting (2020–2021)) was presented to the public and submitted to the Storting in March 2021. This is the sixth plan under the current planning system, covering all modes of transport. The plan presents policies and priorities within an economic frame for a twelve year period and provides perspectives towards 2050.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The National Transport Plan 2022–2033",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "March 2021",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "sixth",
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "a twelve year",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9859890937805176,
            "1": 0.01401088573038578
        }
    },
    "45": {
        "document": "Norway: Tax reduction on EV for company cars reduced from 50 to 40%.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "EV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "50 to 40%",
                "PERCENT"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.050670184195041656,
            "1": 0.9493298530578613
        }
    },
    "46": {
        "document": "Norway: Repeatedly white paper on on National Climate Policy (2001, 2007, 2012)\nCO2 tax: Scattered policy approach that is centrally coordinated but no overarching legally binding framework that passed parliament.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "National Climate Policy",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2001, 2007,",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2012",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.045526523143053055,
            "1": 0.9544734954833984
        }
    },
    "47": {
        "document": "Norway: The support scheme was part of a financial stimulus package after the 2008 fiscal crisis, and funded 100 % of the installation cost for normal chargers, up to NOK 30 000 per charging point. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2008",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "100 %",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "30 000",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9769339561462402,
            "1": 0.02306601218879223
        }
    },
    "48": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Legislative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom:",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.20814372599124908,
            "1": 0.7918562889099121
        }
    },
    "49": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: It is a strategic plan for a Green Industrial Revolution. The ten points that the government will place efforts in the next years are encompasses clean power generation, reduce emissions in industry, transport and building sectors and increase the woodlands in UK to build a path towards a net-zero society.\nAs direct targets, the plan outlines production of 40 GW of offshore wind power by 2030, to have 10Mt of carbon captured per year by 2030 due to investments in CCS. \n ",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "a Green Industrial Revolution",
                "LAW"
            ],
            [
                "ten",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "the next years",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "40",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "10Mt",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "CCS",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9880411624908447,
            "1": 0.011958800256252289
        }
    },
    "50": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Act establishes a legally binding target of at least an 80% cut in GHG emissions by 2050, against a 1990 baseline. It also creates 5-yearly “carbon budgets” as a pathway to meet the long-term target. The fourth carbon budget, for 2023–2027 approved by parliament in 2011 and reviewed in 2014, puts into law a target to reduce emissions by 50% from 1990 levels by 2025 (the midpoint of the budget period).\nThe Committee on Climate Change (CCC) – a new independent, expert body to advise the government on the level of carbon budgets and on progress in meeting these budgets.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "at least an",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "80%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "GHG",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "1990",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "5-yearly",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "fourth",
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2023–2027",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2011",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2014",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "50%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "1990",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2025",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "The Committee on Climate Change (CCC",
                "ORG"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.023994863033294678,
            "1": 0.9760051369667053
        }
    },
    "51": {
        "document": "Norway: Legislative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.25160372257232666,
            "1": 0.7483962774276733
        }
    },
    "52": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Gas boilers in the UK will be replaced by low-carbon heating systems in all new homes built after 2025. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2025",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9692423939704895,
            "1": 0.0307575985789299
        }
    },
    "53": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This roadmap is part of a larger plan to green finance in the UK. It sets out a strategy to deliver on phase 1 of the plan, which is informing investors and consumers – addressing the information gap for market participants, ensuring a flow of decision-useful information on environmental sustainability from corporates to financial market participants. Following phases of the plan will include acting on the information, and shifting financial flows.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "1",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9883861541748047,
            "1": 0.011613822542130947
        }
    },
    "54": {
        "document": "Norway: Introduced in 1999, with differentiated between waste going to landfill and incineration. Incineration tax ended in 2010.\nRates in 2013 are NOK 479 per tonne for biodegradable waste going to landfill, NOK 289 per tonn for other waste going to landfill. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "1999",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2010",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2013",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "479",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "289",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.11867598444223404,
            "1": 0.8813239932060242
        }
    },
    "55": {
        "document": "Norway: EVs cannot be charged more than 50% the fare for fossil fuel cars on ferries.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "more than 50%",
                "PERCENT"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.053074099123477936,
            "1": 0.946925938129425
        }
    },
    "56": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Act contains measures to create a more integrated transport system and provide for a public-private partnership for National Air Traffic Services Ltd (“NATS”). The Act aims to improve local passenger transport services, and reduce road congestion and pollution. The use of railways will be promoted through the Strategic Rail Authority.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "National Air Traffic Services Ltd",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Strategic Rail Authority",
                "ORG"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.8990166187286377,
            "1": 0.1009833812713623
        }
    },
    "57": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Amongst other goals, the 25 years Plan lays out a strategic plan to take action to mitigate emissions and adapt to climate change effects by cutting greenhouse gas emissions including from land use, land use change, the agriculture and waste sectors and the use of fluorinated gases and implementing the Second National Adaptation Programme. Also, the plan outlines a expansion of the woodland cover and support protection of international forests. \nIn the energy sector, the plan outlines a commitment to another policy - the Clean Growth Strategy - underscoring that UK will take action to eliminate unabated coal-fired electricity by 2025.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the 25 years",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Second",
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "the Clean Growth Strategy",
                "LAW"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2025",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.987659752368927,
            "1": 0.012340218760073185
        }
    },
    "58": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: During the 2016 Autumn Statement, the Chancellor announced additional funding of £80m for charging infrastructure (including rapid charge points) for the period 2017 to 2020 and Government is considering how best to allocate this funding to meet the needs of drivers and deliver value for money. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom: During",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the 2016 Autumn Statement",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "80",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "the period 2017 to",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2020",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9856891632080078,
            "1": 0.014310849830508232
        }
    },
    "59": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The UK government will support the CCS Infrastructure Fund to establish CCS in at least two UK sites, one by the mid-2020s, a second by 2030. It aims to establish at least one CO2 capture equipped gas power plant by 2030 with the help of consumer subsidies.\nAlso, the Budget confirms funding for the Heat Networks Investment Project  and provides £270 million of new funding to enable new and existing heat networks to adopt low carbon heat sources in the building sector. The aim is that the heating of homes reaches net-zero by 2050 replacing natural gas and other fossil fuels with low carbon alternatives, such as biomethane.\nFunding in the transport sector to reduce vehicle pollution through purchases and investments in zero emission light vehicles, and in the natural environmental sector to increase environmental restoration are also outlined in the budget plan.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the CCS Infrastructure Fund",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "CCS",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "at least two",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "one",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "the mid-2020s",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "second",
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "at least one",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Budget",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Heat Networks Investment Project",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "£270 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9934548139572144
        }
    },
    "60": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This policy sets out a target of at least 50%, and as many as 70%, of new car sales and up to 40% of new van sales being ultra low emission by 2030.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "at least 50%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "as many as",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "up to 40%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.05251321196556091,
            "1": 0.9474867582321167
        }
    },
    "61": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Net Zero innovation Portfolio establishes a £1 billion fund  for low-carbon technologies and systems to advance decarbonisation in the UK. This fund was announced  in the UK Government's ten point plan.\nThe portfolio outlines offshore wind, CCS, nuclear energy, hydrogen, industrial fuel switch and buildings among the priority areas to invest and support the development of technologies.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Zero",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "£1 billion",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the UK Government's",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "ten",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "CCS",
                "ORG"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9857137799263,
            "1": 0.014286233112215996
        }
    },
    "62": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Energy Technology List is a UK government-managed list of energy-efficient plant and machinery, such as boilers, electric motors, and air conditioning and refrigeration systems that qualify for tax relief under the the Enhanced Capital Allowance tax scheme for businesses. For a product to be on the ETL, it must meet specific energy-saving or energy-efficient criteria. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Energy Technology List",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "ETL",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9869301915168762,
            "1": 0.013069846667349339
        }
    },
    "63": {
        "document": "Norway: The overarching objective of this National Transport Plan is to develop a \"transport system that is safe, enhances value creation and contributes to a low-carbon society\".\nUnder this plan, the Government aims to develop efficient transport corridors and invest more than 400 billion NOK (~ 41 billion €) in roads, railways, coastal infrastructure and aviation in the period 2018 – 2029",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "this National Transport Plan",
                "LAW"
            ],
            [
                "Government",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "more than 400 billion",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "41 billion €",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "the period 2018",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2029",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9864746928215027,
            "1": 0.01352535281330347
        }
    },
    "64": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: The Scottish Biomass Support Scheme was launched in 2006, with GBP 7.5 million in funding over the financial years 2006-07 and 2007-08. The capital grant scheme is applicable to all formally constituted organisations in Scotland, both public and private, of varying sizes (micro-enterprises and SMEs). Barring exceptional circumstances, the maximum capital grant allowed is GBP 400 000. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Scottish Biomass Support Scheme",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2006",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "GBP",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "7.5 million",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "the financial years 2006-07",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2007-08",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Scotland",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9871811270713806,
            "1": 0.012818879447877407
        }
    },
    "65": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Executive",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom: Executive",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.20934638381004333,
            "1": 0.790653645992279
        }
    },
    "66": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Tax benefits for businesses installing charging infrastructure through a 100% first year allowance (FYA) for expenditure incurred on electric vehicle chargepoint equipment. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "100%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "first year",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "FYA",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9672938585281372,
            "1": 0.03270614892244339
        }
    },
    "67": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: LCVIP promoted UK-based R&D and showcased vehicle technologies through demonstrations and road trials. The ULEV programme's aim was “to cement the UK’s position as a leader” in the development of ULEVs. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "ULEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9806730151176453,
            "1": 0.019326966255903244
        }
    },
    "68": {
        "document": "Norway: The Norwegian State Housing Bank assists with achieving Norway's national environmental targets by encouraging the construction of more environment-friendly housing, for example by stimulating low energy consumption. The Housing Bank supports projects that contribute to capacity building; those with a high level of ambition and a high transfer value IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Norwegian State Housing Bank",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Housing Bank",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9875585436820984,
            "1": 0.012441498227417469
        }
    },
    "69": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: A Bill to make provision about targets, plans and policies for improving the natural environment; for statements and reports about environmental protection; for the Office for Environmental Protection; about waste and resource efficiency; about air quality; for the recall of products that fail to meet environmental standards; about water; about nature and biodiversity; for conservation covenants; about the regulation of chemicals; and for connected purposes.\nIncludes provisions for fines for the importation of products or commodities linked to illegal deforestation.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Office for Environmental Protection",
                "ORG"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9892022609710693,
            "1": 0.010797781869769096
        }
    },
    "70": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Legislative IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom: Legislative",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.7978659272193909,
            "1": 0.20213405787944794
        }
    },
    "71": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This funding is in addition to £40 million already committed by the Mayor of London to compensate taxi drivers whose vehicles are affected by new tighter age limits to retire the oldest, most polluting taxis. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "£40 million",
                "MONEY"
            ],
            [
                "London",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.31100860238075256,
            "1": 0.688991367816925
        }
    },
    "72": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Go Ultra Low is a ground-breaking joint government and car industry campaign – supported by the Society for Motor Manufacturers and Traders (SMMT) and the government’s Office for Low Emission Vehicles (OLEV). The aim of the campaign is to provide all the facts and information needed to make an informed decision about switching to an electric vehicle (EV). Through education and information this campaign will help determine the vehicle that fits each indivduals needs. Additional information is provided to help select an EV-friendly tariff and charge at home system. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom: Go Ultra Low",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "–",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "the Society for Motor Manufacturers",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the government’s Office for Low Emission Vehicles",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "OLEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "EV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "EV",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9911848306655884
        }
    },
    "73": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This strategy sets out the UK's plan to increase energy independence, which includes increasing energy efficiency, reducing demand, increasing renewable power generation and increasing domestic production of oil and gas.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.970884382724762,
            "1": 0.02911563403904438
        }
    },
    "74": {
        "document": "Norway: 2015: E85 cars receive a tax deduction of NOK 10000. BEV and FCEV do not pay import tax, nor VAT. PHEV receive a reduction of import tax up to NOK 10000; 2016: E85 cars receive a tax deduction of NOK 10000. BEV and FCEV do not pay import tax, nor VAT.PHEV receive a reduction of import tax up to NOK 10000. This scheme will remain until 2018 and then revised. Free toll roads will probably be replaced with a new system with differentiated prices depending on CO2 and NOx emissions. The original idea was to keep EV tax free until 2020, but lately the Government is thinking of increasing taxes for large EVs liek Tesla model X; 2017: E85 cars receive a tax deduction of NOK 10000. BEV and FCEV do not pay import tax, nor VAT. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2015",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "E85",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "10000",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "BEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "FCEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "VAT",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "PHEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2016",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "E85",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "10000",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "BEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "FCEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2018",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "EV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2020",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Government",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Tesla",
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "2017",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "E85",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "NOK",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "10000",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "BEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "FCEV",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "VAT",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "1": 0.9945194125175476
        }
    },
    "75": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This strategy formulates the UK's plans to develop its CCU industry and attract investors. It aims to capture 20-30 MtCO2e per year by 2030.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "CCU",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "20-30",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "MtCO2e per year",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.3382650315761566,
            "1": 0.6617349982261658
        }
    },
    "76": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Legislative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom:",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.20805613696575165,
            "1": 0.7919438481330872
        }
    },
    "77": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: Legislative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom:",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.2081315815448761,
            "1": 0.7918684482574463
        }
    },
    "78": {
        "document": "Norway: Executive",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.25278422236442566,
            "1": 0.747215747833252
        }
    },
    "79": {
        "document": "Norway: The plan discusses Norway's efforts to reduce methane emissions and identifies the ministries and authorities responsible for implementing methane reduction targets in the various sectors. Methane reduction targets are not identified, but methane is part of the overarching greenhouse gas reduction targets of 55% by 2030 and 90-95% by 2050.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "55%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "90-95%",
                "PERCENT"
            ],
            [
                "2050",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.6220750212669373,
            "1": 0.37792497873306274
        }
    },
    "80": {
        "document": "Norway: Hydropower plants less than 5 MW are exempt from natural resource and ground rent taxes. All new renewable energy (including small scale hydro power) is covered by the electricity certificate scheme. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "MW",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9817488193511963,
            "1": 0.018251212313771248
        }
    },
    "81": {
        "document": "Norway: The scheme of the Centres for Environment-friendly Energy Research (FME) seeks to develop expertise and promote innovation through focus on long-term research in selected areas of environment-friendly energy. There are today 11 centres within renewable energy, energy efficiency, social sciences and CO2-management. The research activity is carried out in close cooperation between prominent research communities and users. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Centres for Environment-friendly Energy Research",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "FME",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "today",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "11",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9888890385627747,
            "1": 0.011110919527709484
        }
    },
    "82": {
        "document": "Norway: EVs are not required to pay toll roads and ferries.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.06145753711462021,
            "1": 0.9385424852371216
        }
    },
    "83": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This strategic policy document sets out a target of 5GW of low-carbon hydrogen production capacity in the UK by 2030. According to the government, the use of low carbon hydrogen enabled by 5GW production capacity could deliver total emissions savings of around 41MtCO2e between 2023 and 2032, equivalent to the carbon captured by 700 million trees over the same time period.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "5GW",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2030",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "5GW",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "41MtCO2e",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "between 2023 and 2032",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "700 million",
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9822399020195007,
            "1": 0.017760084941983223
        }
    },
    "84": {
        "document": "Norway: In parking areas, there is to be provided charging capacity for rechargeable motor vehicle in a sufficient number of parking spaces, that is to say that there is generally a free space at all times with charging possibilities. However, the company is not obliged to offer charging possibilities of more than six per cent of the total number of places. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "more than six",
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Measures Database",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "OECD",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "November 2020",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.022647613659501076,
            "1": 0.9773523807525635
        }
    },
    "85": {
        "document": "United Kingdom: This policy applies to hydropower, anaerobic digestion, wind and solar PV technologies under 5MW. The FiT lasts between 10 and 25 years, according to the technology. A scheme was also implemented for micro CHP (end of application period on 31 March 2019: https://energysavingtrust.org.uk/renewable-energy/electricity/micro-chp).\nFor details, refer to the sources below.",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United Kingdom",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "PV",
                "FAC"
            ],
            [
                "under 5MW",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "FiT",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "between 10 and 25 years",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "CHP",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "31 March 2019",
                "DATE"
            ]
        ],
        "topics": {
            "0": 0.9685841202735901,
            "1": 0.0314159132540226
        }
    },
    "86": {
        "document": "Norway: The first NDC of Norway includes a commitment reduce greenhouse gas emissions by at least 40% compared to 1990 levels, by 2030. The emission reduction target will be developed into an emissions budget covering the period 2021-2030. IEA/IRENA Global Renewable Energy Policies and Measures Database © OECD/IEA and IRENA, [November 2020]",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "first",
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "at least 40%",
